Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (VADP); Records apap304
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administration, 1984-2023; 1; 2.2 cubic ft.; 3.39 GB
  - Former Board Members List, 2016 May 18
  - Former Board Members List, 2016 June 7
  - Former Board Members List, 2018 November 6
  - Fund Nonviolence Death Penalty Mobilization Fund Grant Short Request, 2020 October 15
  - Fundraiser Database Export, 2011 May 3
  - Fundraising Documents, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Fundraising Letter 2022 Final, 2022 November; 2022 November 7
  - Fundraising Letter 2022, Draft, 2022 April; 2022 March 23
  - Fundraising Letter 2022, Draft, 2022 April; 2022 March 25
  - Fundraising Letter 2022, Draft, 2022 April; 2022 March 21
  - Fundraising Letter 2022, Draft Edits by Dan Shaw, 2022 April; 2022 March 30
  - Fundraising Letter 2022, Final, 2022 April; 2022 March 31
  - Fundraising Letter 2023, Draft, 2023 April; 2023 March 23
  - Fundraising Letter 2023, Draft, 2023 April; 2023 March 27
  - Fundraising Letter 2023, Final, 2023 April; 2023 March 30
  - Fundraising Letter Draft, 2020 April; 2020 March 16; 2020 April 10
  - Fundraising Letter Draft, 2020 April; 2020 March 17; 2020 April 10
  - Fundraising Letter Draft, 2020 April; 2020 March 18; 2020 April 10
  - Fundraising Letter Draft, 2020 April; 2020 March 24; 2020 April 10
  - Fundraising Letter Draft, 2020 April; 2020 March 25; 2020 April 10
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 1, 2017 April
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 1, 2017 November; 2017 October 30
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 1, 2018 April
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 1, 2018 November; 2018 October 22
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 1, 2019 April
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 1, 2019 November
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 1, 2020 November; 2020 October 9
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 1, 2021 April; 2021 April 19
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 2, 2017 April
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 2, 2017 November; 2017 October 31
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 2, 2018 November; 2018 October 24
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 2, 2019 April
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 2, 2019 November
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 2, 2020 November; 2020 October 9
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 2, 2021 April; 2021 April 21
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 2, Dan Shaw, 2018 April
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 3, 2017 April
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 3, 2017 November; 2017 November 8
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 3, 2018 April
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 3, 2018 November; 2018 October 25
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 3, 2019 April
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 3, 2019 November
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 3, 2020 November; 2020 October 9
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 3, Dan Shaw, 2021 April; 2021 April 26
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 3, Dan Shaw Revised, 2021 April; 2021 April 26
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 4, 2017 November; 2017 November 8
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 4 Dan Shaw Version 1, 2019 November
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 4 Dan Shaw Version 2, 2019 November
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 4, Dan Shaw, 2019 April
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 4, Paul O'Shea, 2018 November; 2018 November 1
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 5, 2017 November; 2017 November 8
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 5, 2019 April
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 5 Version 1 House Flips, 2019 November
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 5 Version 2 House Stays Republican, 2019 November
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 5, Dan Shaw, 2018 November; 2018 November 1
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 6, 2017 November; 2017 November 9
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 6, 2018 November; 2018 November 2
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 6, 2019 April
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 6 Version 1 House Flips, 2019 November
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 7, 2017 November; 2017 November 13
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 7, 2018 November; 2018 November 2
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 7 Version 1 House Flips, 2019 November
  - Fundraising Letter Draft 7 Version 2 House Stays Republican, 2019 November
  - Fundraising Letter Draft from Dan Shaw, 2016 May; 2016 May 3
  - Fundraising Letter Draft from Dan Shaw, 2021 November; 2021 November 13
  - Fundraising Letter Draft, Revised, 2020 April; 2020 March 25; 2020 April 10
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations, 2019 November; 2019 December 31; 2020 January 1
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2016 May; 2016 July 22
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2016 May; 2016 November 21
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2016 November; 2017 January 5
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2016 November; 2017 January 11
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2016 November; 2017 January 18
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2016 November; 2017 March 3
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2017 April; 2017 June 20
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2017 November; 2018 January 4; 2018 January 9
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2017 November; 2018 January 19; 2018 January 18
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2018 April; 2019 May 7
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2018 November; 2019 January 4
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2019 April; 2019 June 7
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2019 April
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2020 April; 2020 June 4
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2020 April; 2020 April 23
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2020 November; 2021 January 4
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2020 November; 2021 January 7
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2021 May; 2021 June 3
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2021 May; 2021 June 9
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2021 December; 2022 February 3
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2022 April; 2022 June 3
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2022 November; 2023 January 10
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2022 November; 2023 January 25
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2023 April; 2023 May 24
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, 2023 April; 2023 June 6
  - Fundraising Letter Expenses & Donations Generated, Final, 2016 November; 2017 March 3
  - Fundraising Letter Final, 2021 April; 2021 May 10
  - Fundraising Letter Final, 2021 November; 2021 November 13
  - Fundraising Letter Final on Letterhead, 2022 November; 2022 November 7
  - Fundraising Letter Final with Letterhead, 2021 November; 2021 November 18
  - Fundraising Letter Final with Logo, 2021 April; 2021 May 10
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Appeal on Letterhead, 2019 November; 2019 November 7
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Donors, 2016 November; 2016 November 28
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Donors Current, 2017 November; 2017 November 13
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Donors Current, 2018 April; 2018 April 27
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Donors Current, 2019 April; 2019 April 1
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Donors Current, 2019 November; 2019 November 4
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Donors Current, 2020 November; 2020 October 23
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Donors Not Current, 2017 November; 2017 November 13
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Donors Not Current, 2018 April; 2018 April 3
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Donors Not Current, 2019 April; 2019 April 1
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Donors Not Current, 2019 November; 2019 November 4
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Donors Not Current, 2020 November; 2020 October 23
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Generic Appeal on Letterhead, 2019 November; 2019 November 7
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Generic Appeal on Letterhead, 2020 November; 2020 October 29
  - Fundraising Letter Final, NonDonors, 2016 November; 2016 November 12
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Not Donors, 2017 November; 2017 November 21
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Not Donors, 2018 April; 2018 April 3
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Not Donors, 2019 April; 2019 April 1
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Not Donors, 2019 November; 2019 November 4
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Not Donors, 2020 November; 2020 October 23
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Reponse Card, 2022 April; 2022 March 31
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Response Card, 2016 November; 2016 November 28
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Response Card, 2017 November; 2017 November 13
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Response Card, 2018 April; 2018 April 2
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Response Card, 2021 May; 2021 April 21
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Response Card, 2021 December; 2021 November 18
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Response Cards, 2022 November; 2022 November 7
  - Fundraising Letter Final, Victor Glasberg, 2017 April; 2017 April 17; 2017 April 29
  - Fundraising Letter Final. Letterhead, 2016 November; 2016 December 20
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients Final, 2021 December
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients Raw, 2021 December
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Bad Addresses, 2021 May; 2021 June 10
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Cleaned Up, 2020 April; 2020 March 26
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Cleaned Up, 2020 November; 2020 October 23
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Cleaned Up, 2021 May; 2021 April 14
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Donors Current, 2017 April; 2017 April 7
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Donors Current, 2017 November; 2017 November 13
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Donors Current, 2018 April; 2018 April 9
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Donors Current, 2018 November
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Donors Current, 2019 April; 2019 April 1
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Donors Current, 2019 November; 2019 November 5
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Donors Current, 2020 April; 2020 March 27
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Donors Current, 2020 November; 2020 October 23
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Donors Not Current, 2017 April; 2017 April 7
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Donors Not Current, 2017 November; 2017 November 13
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Donors Not Current, 2018 April; 2018 April 9
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Donors Not Current, 2018 November
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Donors Not Current, 2019 April; 2019 April 1
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Donors Not Current, 2019 November; 2020 March 27
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Donors Not Current, 2020 April; 2020 March 27
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Donors Not Current, 2020 November; 2020 October 23
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Final, 2022 April
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Final, 2022 November; 2022 November 7
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Final, 2023 April; 2023 March 29
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Final, 2023 November; 2023 October 25
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Name but No Contact Info (Delete), 2018 April; 2018 April 13
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, New Addresses, 2021 May; 2021 June 10
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, New Addresses Revised, 2021 May; 2021 June 17
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, No Address Delete Unsubscribed, 2018 April; 2018 April 13
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, No Name To Be Deleted, 2018 April; 2018 April 13
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Not Donor, 2019 November; 2019 November 5
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Not Donors, 2017 April; 2017 April 7
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Not Donors, 2017 November; 2017 November 13
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Not Donors, 2018 April; 2018 April 9
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Not Donors, 2018 November
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Not Donors, 2019 April; 2019 April 1
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Not Donors, 2020 April; 2020 March 27
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Not Donors, 2020 November; 2020 October 23
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Raw, 2017 April; 2017 April 7
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Raw, 2017 November; 2017 November 13
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Raw, 2018 April; 2018 April 9
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Raw, 2018 November
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Raw, 2019 April; 2019 April 1
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Raw, 2019 November; 2019 November 4
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Raw, 2020 April; 2020 March 26
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Raw, 2020 November; 2020 October 23
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Raw, 2021 May; 2021 April 14
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Raw, 2022 April
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Raw, 2022 November; 2022 November 7
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Raw, 2023 April; 2023 March 29
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Raw, 2023 November; 2023 October 25
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Raw Cleaned Up, 2019 November; 2019 November 5
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Raw Sorted, 2018 April; 2018 April 9
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Raw, Revised, 2018 November
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Sorted by Date, 2018 November
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Sorted by Most Recent Donations, 2019 November; 2019 November 5
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Updated Addresses from Mailing, 2019 April; 2019 May 17
  - Fundraising Letter List of Recipients, Very Raw, 2018 April; 2018 April 13
  - Fundraising Letter Severe Mental Illness Version, 2018 April; 2018 March 16
  - Fundraising Letter to Campaign Donor List, Draft, 2019 June; 2019 May 14; 2019 June 1
  - Fundraising Letter to Campaign Donor List, Draft, 2019 June; 2019 May 20; 2019 June 1
  - Fundraising Letter to Campaign Donor List, Draft, 2019 June; 2019 May 21; 2019 June 1
  - Fundraising Letter to Campaign Donor List, Draft, 2019 June; 2019 May 23; 2019 June 1
  - Fundraising Letter to Campaign Donor List, Draft, 2019 June; 2019 May 30; 2019 June 7
  - Fundraising Letter to Campaign Donor List, Draft, 2019 June; 2019 May 31; 2019 June 7
  - Fundraising Letter to Campaign Donor List, Final, 2019 June; 2019 June 7; 2019 June 10
  - Fundraising Letter to Campaign Donor List, Funds Generated, 2019 June; 2019 July 11
  - Fundraising Letter to Campaign Donor List, Merged, 2019 June; 2019 June 7; 2019 June 10
  - Fundraising Letter to Campaign Donor List, Merged Revised, 2019 June; 2019 June 13; 2019 June 10
  - Fundraising Letter to Campaign Donor List, Response Card A, 2019 June; 2019 May 28
  - Fundraising Letter to Campaign Donor List, Response Card B, 2019 June; 2019 May 28
  - Fundraising Letter to Lawyers, Final, 2015 December 3; 2015 December 2
  - Fundraising Letter, Address Changes, 2021 December; 2022 March 17
  - Fundraising Letter, Address Changes, 2023 April; 2023 May 23
  - Fundraising Letter, Adresses Changes, 2022 April; 2022 June 8
  - Fundraising Letter, Bill from Comm Mailing Systems #13079, 2017 April
  - Fundraising Letter, Corrected Addresses, 2017 April
  - Fundraising Letter, Draft, 2022 November; 2022 October 25
  - Fundraising Letter, Draft, 2022 November; 2022 October 26
  - Fundraising Letter, Draft 1, 2016 May; 2016 April 21
  - Fundraising Letter, Draft 1, 2016 November
  - Fundraising Letter, Draft 2, 2016 May; 2016 April 25
  - Fundraising Letter, Draft 2, 2016 November
  - Fundraising Letter, Draft 3, 2016 May; 2016 May 3
  - Fundraising Letter, Draft 3, from Dan Shaw, 2016 November
  - Fundraising Letter, Draft 4, 2016 May; 2016 May 5
  - Fundraising Letter, Draft 4, 2016 November
  - Fundraising Letter, Draft 5, 2016 November
  - Fundraising Letter, Draft Edits with Dan Shaw, 2022 November; 2022 November 3
  - Fundraising Letter, Draft Version A, 2023 November; 2023 October 25
  - Fundraising Letter, Draft Version B, 2023 November; 2023 October 25
  - Fundraising Letter, Final, 2016 May; 2016 May 5
  - Fundraising Letter, Final, 2023 November; 2023 November 8
  - Fundraising Letter, Final, Donors Current, 2017 April; 2017 April 7; 2017 April 17
  - Fundraising Letter, Final, Donors Current, 2018 November; 2019 December 5
  - Fundraising Letter, Final, Donors Current, 2020 April; 2020 March 25
  - Fundraising Letter, Final, Donors Not Current, 2017 April; 2017 April 7; 2017 April 17
  - Fundraising Letter, Final, Donors Not Current, 2018 November; 2018 November 5
  - Fundraising Letter, Final, Donors Not Current, 2020 April; 2020 March 25
  - Fundraising Letter, Final, Not Donors, 2017 April; 2017 April 7; 2017 April 17
  - Fundraising Letter, Final, Not Donors, 2018 November; 2018 November 5
  - Fundraising Letter, Final, Not Donors, 2020 April; 2020 March 25
  - Fundraising Letter, Final, Sample, 2018 November; 2018 December 4
  - Fundraising Letter,Fianl, 2023 November; 2023 November 10
  - Fundraising Notes "85k by June 30", 2008 September 26
  - General Electric Electric Chair Cartoon by Kent Willis, 1988; 2021 August 19
  - Giving Day Webinar, Chronicle of Philanthropy, 2015 September 25
  - Giving Day Workbook, 2015 September 25
  - Google Analytics Summary- Data by Month, 2021 March 17
  - Govenor Kaine Notes, 2008 October 1
  - Grant Donation Documents, 2017 February-2021 April (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Grant History Document, 2011 May 5
  - Graphic for Making Change Radio "Railroaded" Talk with Dale Brumfield, 2020; 2021 May 27
  - Graphic of House Death Penalty Abolition Floor Vote, 2021 February 5
  - Graphic of Map of Virginia and Number of Executions by County, Labels Large, 1976-2018; 2019 April 5
  - Graphic of William & Mary Zoom Event with Joe Giarratano and Dale Brumfield, 2021 February 19; 2021 May 27
  - Grass Roots Meetings, 2003-2005 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Greg Gelburd Biography, Undated
  - Guide Star Article "Finding Effective Board Members: May Question of the Month Results", 2007 September 20
  - Hampton Inn Fairfax City Reservation for Four Rooms, 2019 March 23-2019 March 24
  - Helen Cobban Board Member Agreement with VADP, 2009 September 27; 2009 October 3
  - History of Executive Board Membership, 2008-2009
  - History of Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, 2007 October
  - History of Virginians for Alternatives to the Death Penalty, 2007 October; 2011 April 8
  - House of Delegates Survey, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Howell, Senate District 32 Constiutents, Report, 2010 February 17
  - "Hunter" Biograpgy, Undated
  - Hunter Mafry Board Member Agreement with VADP, 2007 October 10
  - Image Joe Giarranto Article in Style "Free Man Walking", 2018 May 2; 2018 May 5
  - Image of Aimal Khan Kasi Execution Vigil at Jarratt, 2002 November; 2021 July 11
  - Image of Albert Monroe & Keith DeBlasio, 2005; 2021 November 12
  - Image of Auburn Mitchell, 2009 September 15
  - Image of Barry Weinstein & Robert Hall Respond to Media, 2006; 2012 November 21
  - Image of Barry Weinstein, Esq, 2006 May 4; 2021 November 12
  - Image of Beth, Cropped, 2011 July 11
  - Image of Beverly Monroe, 2019 January 17
  - Image of Bill Pelke of Journey of Hope speaks to St. anne's Bellfield Students and Faculty, 2004 October 26; 2021 November 12
  - Image of Board Meeting, 2002; 2021 November 12
  - Image of Board Meeting, 2018 January 19
  - Image of Board Meeting in "Chville", 2015 September 19; 2015 September 25
  - Image of Board Retreat, 2012; 2023 August 19
  - Image of Board Retreat for Web, 2012; 2012 September 21
  - Image of Board Retreat, Cropped, 2012; 2023 August 19
  - Image of Capital Defense Attorneys, 2018; 2021 August 18
  - Image of Capitol Bell Protest, 2009 February 20; 2009 August 12
  - Image of Chris Marshall, David Saunier & Howard Zehr, 2005 November 12
  - Image of "Chville" Execution Vigil, 2015 October 1; 2017 January 8
  - Image of "Chville" Friend-Raiser, 2017 June 27; 2017 July 4
  - Image of "Chville" Regular Meeting, 2015 November 11; 2015 November 27
  - Image of "Chville" Regular Meeting, 2015 April; 2015 April 24
  - Image of "Chville" Regular Meeting, 2016 May 4; 2016 May 24
  - Image of "Chville" Regular Meeting, 2017 May 16; 2017 May 17
  - Image of "Chville" Regular Meeting, 2017 November 8
  - Image of "Chville" Regular Meeting, 2018 April 26
  - Image of Conference with Betty Gallagher & Paul Blackburn, 2004; 2021 November 12
  - Image of Conference with JPT, 2021 November 12
  - Image of Conference with Mitch Van Yhres, Alan Gell, and Ida Reid, 2004; 2021 November 12
  - Image of Conservatives Concerned About the Death Penalty at YAL with Dale, 2018 May 14
  - Image of Corinna Lain & Jerry Givens at UR, 2015 September 24; 2015 September 25
  - Image of "Cville" Vigil for Percy Walton, 2006; 2021 November 12
  - Image of Dale Recinella, JD, 2006 March 27
  - Image of David Bruck, 2017 August 2
  - Image of David Saunier, Director Central VA, RJ & Howard Zehr, 2005 November 12
  - Image of Death Penalty Forum, 2017 November 14
  - Image of Death Penalty Headlines, 2020-2021; 2021 January 8
  - Image of Debi Cornwall with Pam & Earl Washington Jr., 2021 November 12
  - Image of Delegate Eisenberg VADP NOVA, 2003 February; 2021 November 12
  - Image of Delegate Mitch Van Yaarheed at VADP's Restorative Justice & the Death Penalty, 2005 November 12
  - Image of Diann R-T & Bishop Walter Sullivan at Faith & Values, 2005; 2021 November 12
  - Image of Earl & Jack at Federal Building, 2021 November 12
  - Image of Earl and Pam Washington & Marie Deans, 2003; 2021 November 12
  - Image of Earl Washingtin & Legal Team in "Cville", 2006; 2012 November 21
  - Image of Ed Morrison and John Sheldon, 2004; 2021 November 12
  - Image of Edds Speaking at VADP Conference, 2003; 2021 November 12
  - Image of Engle Hires, 2012 June 7
  - Image of Engle Hires, Cropped, 2012 June 7
  - Image of Engle, Slideshow, 2012 December 19
  - Image of Engle, Smaller, 2012 June 7
  - Image of Eric Columbus at VADP's Restorative Justice & the Death Penalty, 2005 November 12; 2021 November 12
  - Image of Exoneree Michael Graham at VADP's Restorative Justice & the Death Penalty Conference, 2005 November 12
  - Image of Fashion Fundraiser by Murder Victims Families Linnell Patterson, 2010 December 3; 2021 July 16
  - Image of Fast & Vigil, Crowd, 2009 July; 2021 July 16
  - Image of Fast & Vigil, Marisa with Sign, 2009 July; 2021 July 16
  - Image of Fast & Vigil, SCOTUS, 2009 July; 2009 August 17
  - Image of Former VADP Ex-Director, 2011 May; 2011 May 17
  - Image of GAB Supporters, 2010 February 15; 2010 March 5
  - Image of Grandin Theatre- Linda, Michael, and Beth, 2008 October 15; 2021 July 16
  - Image of Greg, 2012 April 26
  - Image of Group Dinner, 2023 September 19
  - Image of Helena Cobban, Cropped, 2012 October 2
  - Image of Helena, Cropped, 2012 April 22
  - Image of "Helena Cobban, LR, Alfie" at Berkeley, 2012 January 18
  - Image of Henry Heller Speaking, 1995; 2021 May 27
  - Image of Horizaontal Logo, High-Resolution, 2015 July 16
  - Image of Jack at Faith & Values Conference, 2005; 2021 November 12
  - Image of JAM Vigil, Line to Ring the Bell, 2009 November 10; 2021 July 16
  - Image of JAM Vigil, Participants Photograph 2, 2009 November 10; 2021 July 16
  - Image of JAM Vigil, Terri, 2009 November 10; 2009 November 13
  - Image of Jerry Givens, 2011 May 18
  - Image of Jerry Givens, 2011 December 22
  - Image of Joe Girrantano Demonstration, 1995; 2021 May 27
  - Image of Jonathan Sheldon, 2005; 2021 November 12
  - Image of Lauren Ramseur, 2012 January 9
  - Image of Lee Statue with Graffiti, 2020 June; 2021 March 31
  - Image of Libertarian Meeting, 2015 April; 2015 April 16
  - Image of Linell & MES in "Chville", 2012 January; 2012 June 17